Genius is forever
Pavarotti is a documentary, history, music film directed by Ron Howard.
Featuring never-before-seen footage, concert performances and intimate interviews, filmmaker
Ron Howard examines the life and career of famed opera tenor Luciano Pavarotti.
Self (archive footage), played by Luciano Pavarotti.
Self, played by Bono.
Self, played by Harvey Goldsmith.
Self, played by Nicoletta Mantovani.
Self, played by Plácido Domingo.
Self, played by José Carreras.
Pavarotti is a 2019 documentary film directed by Ron Howard
about Italian operatic tenor Luciano Pavarotti.
The film had a nationwide premiere event through Fathom Events on June
4, 2019, and was released in theaters on June 7, 2019.
Pavarotti is an American-British venture, with CBS Films
and HanWay Films serving as distributors.
The film explores themes of artists' life, interview,
biography, archive footage, opera singer.